[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Cancer is considered a pandemic.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Dodgeball, which team did not play in the dodgeball tournament in Las Vegas?", "correct_answer": "Go Balls Deep", "incorrect_answers": ["Skillz that Killz", "The Kamikazes", "The Lumberjacks"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Is there any evidence that Triceratops lived in herds?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Sun creates its radiation (heat) by the nuclear fusion between which two elements?", "correct_answer": "Hydrogen and Helium", "incorrect_answers": ["Helium and Oxygen", "Carbon and Helium", "Hydrogen and Carbon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these actors turned down the role of Jason Bourne?", "correct_answer": "Brad Pitt", "incorrect_answers": ["Charlie Sheen", "Ed Burns", "Ben Affleck"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which Odd film was set in Northern Ireland?", "correct_answer": "Odd Man Out", "incorrect_answers": ["Odd Jobs", "Odd Couple", "Odds Against Tomorrow"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the main reason for the extinction of the Moa?", "correct_answer": "It was hunted by man for food.", "incorrect_answers": ["There was not enough room on the island for so many large birds", "It could easily be caught by predators.", "It got to large to support itself."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "After the proof of a mathematical theorem we often see the letters Q.E.D. Do these letters stand for Quite easily Done.?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This American-born actors father was a French diplomat with the United Nations, so he grew up in Geneva, Switzerland, then moved to France at 16. He is most famous for his role as Connor MacLeod.", "correct_answer": "Christopher Lambert", "incorrect_answers": ["Johnny Depp", "Eric Beaumard", "Laurence Olivier"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following movies does this quote come from?\nKarkaroffs Aide: May I have your arm? \nParvati Patil: Arm, leg, Im yours.", "correct_answer": "Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire", "incorrect_answers": ["The Lord of the Rings: The Return of the King", "Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets", "The Lord of the Rings: The Two Towers"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This person, who in 1919 became the General Manager of Radio Corporation of America (RCA), claimed  that he was the first person to receive a signal from the sinking Titanic in 1912.", "correct_answer": "David Sarnoff", "incorrect_answers": ["Leonhard Dresdorff", "Burr Tilstrom", "Capt. Jonas Bray"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Beatles single, that ran seven minutes, was the first to be released on the Beatles new Apple label?", "correct_answer": "Hey, Jude", "incorrect_answers": ["Let It Be", "Revolution", "The Long and Winding Road"]}]